[
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_02_TalkTo_Skye_HelpAidyn",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_02_TEMP_FirstCustomer_TalkToSkye_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_02_TEMP_FirstCustomer_TalkToSkye_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_02a_TalkTo_Shailyn_HelpCurse",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_02a_TEMP_TheCurse_TalkToShailyn_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_02a_TEMP_TheCurse_TalkToShailyn_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_02a_TalkTo_Skye_AnswerCurse",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_02a_TEMP_TheCurse_TalkToSkye_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_02a_TEMP_TheCurse_TalkToSkye_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "Topic_95_s01_02a_TalkTo_Skye_AnswerCurse",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_03a_TalkTo_Grace_ReadyInterviews",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_tavern_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_tavern_talkto",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_04_TalkTo_Zander_FirstMeet",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_TalkTo_FirstMeet_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_TalkTo_FirstMeet_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_04_TalkTo_Eynon_HelpSalve",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_TalkToEynon_HelpSalve_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_TalkToEynon_HelpSalve_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Granny_Zander",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Granny_Zander_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Granny_Zander_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Marty",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Marty_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Marty_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Amis",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Amis_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Amis_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Dicun_Investigate",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Dicun_Investigate_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Dicun_Investigate_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Dicun_CaughtStealing",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Dicun_CaughtStealing_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Dicun_CaughtStealing_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Granny_ZanderCanJoin",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Granny_ZanderCanJoin_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Granny_ZanderCanJoin_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Zander_CanJoin",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Zander_CanJoin_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Zander_CanJoin_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Zander_CaughtPriest"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_05_TalkTo_Zander_CaughtPriest",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Zander_CaughtPriest_topicprompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_TalkTo_Zander_CaughtPriest_cue",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "!95_s01_05_DicunGetsAwayTimeline",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_06_TalkTo_Skye_Impatient",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_TalkTo_Skye_Impatient_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_TalkTo_Skye_Impatient_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": "Topic_95_s01_06_TalkTo_Skye_Straight,Topic_95_s01_06_TalkTo_Skye_Joke,Topic_95_s01_06_TalkTo_Skye_Flirt"
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_06_TalkTo_Skye_Straight",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_TalkToSkye_Straight_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_TalkToSkye_Straight_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "95_s01_skye_straight",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_06_TalkTo_Skye_Joke",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_TalkToSkye_Joke_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_TalkToSkye_Joke_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "95_s01_skye_joke",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_06_TalkTo_Skye_Flirt",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_TalkToSkye_Flirt_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_TalkToSkye_Flirt_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "95_s01_skye_flirt",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_06_TalkTo_Fergus_GoAway",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_TalkTo_Fergus_GoAway_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_TalkTo_Fergus_GoAway_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_06_TalkTo_Fergus_GetInfo",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_TalkTo_Fergus_GetInfo_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_06_TEMP_SupplyChains_TalkTo_Fergus_GetInfo_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_07_TalkTo_Zander_Fire",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_07_TEMP_PossibilitiesOfFire_TalkTo_Zander_Fire_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_07_TEMP_PossibilitiesOfFire_TalkTo_Zander_Fire_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_08_TalkTo_Grace_AidynCaptured",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_08_TEMP_HotOnTheTrail_TalkTo_Grace_AidynCaptured_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_08_TEMP_HotOnTheTrail_TalkTo_Grace_AidynCaptured_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_08_TalkTo_Skye_AidynCaptured",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_08_TEMP_HotOnTheTrail_TalkTo_Skye_AidynCaptured_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_08_TEMP_HotOnTheTrail_TalkTo_Skye_AidynCaptured_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_09_TalkTo_Skye_Faceless",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_09_TEMP_Faceless_TalkTo_Skye_Hiding_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_09_TEMP_Faceless_TalkTo_Skye_Hiding_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_09_TalkTo_Zander_Faceless",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_09_TEMP_Faceless_TalkTo_Zander_Hiding_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_09_TEMP_Faceless_TalkTo_Zander_Hiding_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_09_TalkTo_Dog_Faceless",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_09_TEMP_Faceless_TalkTo_Dog_Hiding_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_09_TEMP_Faceless_TalkTo_Dog_Hiding_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_10_TalkTo_Skye_Styrkr",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_ToBeContinued_TalkTo_Skye_Styrkr_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_ToBeContinued_TalkTo_Skye_Styrkr_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_10_TalkTo_Skye_WrapStraight",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_ToBeContinued_TalkTo_Skye_Wrap_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_ToBeContinued_TalkTo_Skye_Wrap_Straight_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "95_s01_skye_straight",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_10_TalkTo_Skye_WrapJoke",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_ToBeContinued_TalkTo_Skye_Wrap_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_ToBeContinued_TalkTo_Skye_Wrap_Joke_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "95_s01_skye_joke",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_10_TalkTo_Skye_WrapFlirt",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_ToBeContinued_TalkTo_Skye_Wrap_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_ToBeContinued_TalkTo_Skye_Wrap_Flirt_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "95_s01_skye_flirt",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_10_TalkTo_Zander_Wrap",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_ToBeContinued_TalkTo_Zander_Wrap_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_ToBeContinued_TalkTo_Zander_Wrap_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_10_TalkTo_Dog_Wrap",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_ToBeContinued_TalkTo_Dog_Wrap_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_ToBeContinued_TalkTo_Dog_Wrap_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_95_s01_10_TalkTo_Grace_Wrap",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_ToBeContinued_TalkTo_Grace_Wrap_prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95_s01_10_TEMP_ToBeContinued_TalkTo_Grace_Wrap_next",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    }
]
